This time, Iriko is planning to drive.
They talk about various things in the car while driving alone.
And they eat and eat and eat at an oyster hut in Itoshima!
Watch till the end!
Good morning!
Today I'd like to go on location with just the two of you.
We're going to visit an oyster hut.
Yay, persimmons!
I'm so happy!
I love it.
I love it! It's really just the two of you.
In the car.
Isn't it the first time.
It's the first time we've been completely alone together.
-
Batten down the hatches.
Come on. Let's go.
You want me to go? Yes, I'm on my way.
Are you a navigator, Natoru?
It looks like Natrule, Ai.
Wait, wait, wait.
Which one is Navi?
I'm walking around.
Left!
It's pretty far left. 200 meters.
Okay, 200 meters.
Is that the next traffic light?
I don't know. Maybe... maybe... maybe I'm in the right place.
Yes! Yes!
We can go straight.
What's that? This one.
Is that right?
Yeah, but up there?
Yeah, it goes up and then to the right.
Okay, then.
If I go up there, I might not go down there.
Are you sure you're not going the other way? Backwards?
Backwards?
This one.
What? I thought it was this way.
Is it straight ahead?
But I can't go any further.
Can we go now?
Once I say this...
Well, we'll figure it out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mister...
Yes, is this it?
Here it is.
There's a card in there with the theme of the car.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
So, Riko, what number do you want?
How many cards do you have?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Okay, third, please.
One, two, three.
That's it!
Third one from this side, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Third one from this side? All of them? Jan-jan, here you go. Two hearts for the two of you about to get a new member.
New members?
No, they're finally coming in.
This is the second time we're welcoming a new member.
Yes, we have a new member coming in.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. We're the second time we're welcoming a new member.
How's it going? What do you think?
I'm not sure yet.
Really?
This way.
If you turn right, you turn right, right?
This is right.
There's another kilometer to go.
Let's go again.
Yeah... we have a new member.
New member...
But still...
I'm looking forward to it.
Bigger.
When a new member comes in...
When the new member comes in, the new member will probably..,
What do you say?
Yes! I'm sure they'll say, “Yes!
I can get caught up in that feeling.
Yes, I think so.
When RiruMiyu joined us, they was quite young and fresh.
We also felt that we had to do our best to keep up with them.
But, you know, with Rirumiyu, it was our first time, so we had a lot of things we didn't know,
But this time, it was only our second time, so we felt like we should have done more.
It's all around, isn't it?
Yeah.
The sound is right.
Yes, that's right.
I hope I can make the most of it.
It's the way to go.
Oh, it's so cute!
Hiragana
It's “Michinari”.
Yes, it is.
But it's kind of like “Michinari”...
Yeah.
I mean...
Is it a street?
I've never seen it before.
I know what you mean.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what they say.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Usually.
Isn't this a turn? There are times when the road is like that.
Yes, it does.
This really is a turn.
It feels good.
It's getting to be a good time.
But I'm comfortable in the passenger seat.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a convenience store here.
Yes, there is.
It's hard to see on the right.
Yeah, it'd be nice.
Would you go for this?
Should I go? This is...
Yes, you should.
Okay, yes, in the middle, please.
Ta-da!
What's Miyu Yanagi like? Miyu?
Like that? Heart of a cue?
Cue heart, Miyu-chan.
What's she like?
Surprisingly, she's the hardest to catch.
I know, I know.
I know.
Even now, I still see this side of you, and this side of you, and this side of you, and this side of you, and the more I spend time with you, the more I discover more and more things about you.
Unearthing? I know what you mean.
At first, I thought she was a quiet girl.
That's the image I had.
But when I was with her, I found out that she's not like that. She's a messing around girl.
Well, she does seem a little strange, doesn't she?
That's for sure.
Sometimes I feel like she really spends a lot of time on her own.
Even during lessons.
I've been working for almost an hour now.
I think I'm going to pass the baton to Ai-chan at the next convenience store.
Is there a convenience store near here?
I wonder if I can turn this thing around?
That's fine.
Straight ahead.
Looks good.
We can go to Saga.
Oh, Itoshima!
What a surprise!
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
Itoshima.
I can see the letters.
I see it. Yes, I see it.
We're almost there.
But I can't get to this convenience store.
I wonder if it's there.
It's from the top.
Not yet.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're going to teach me, aren't you?
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait.
What's up?
What's wrong?
It's scary... it's so light!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Pedestrians? Poiler.
What's Haruna Keena like?
What's she like?
We talk about everything, don't we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's on your mind right now.
Or what happened today.
We talk a lot, but Keena translates it all.
She doesn't talk much.
So I wonder what he usually does.
I know, I know... Keener's personal life is a mystery to me.
It is a mystery, isn't it?
So maybe he's just the right person for the job... even though he's tempted to talk.
I'm tempted to talk to him like this, but he listens to me.
Balance.
Balance? Balancer?
I don't know.
Maybe a better sense of balance.
What's it called?
He talks a lot, but I can handle it.
I don't know.
They talk a lot.
Maybe that's what it sounds like.
Oh, I ate!
I'm pretty sure they won't come outside.
It was like a sweet potato.
Did I lie?
They'll come inside, too.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
We're here.
Mr. Dowd.
I'm glad we're here.
How did you write that?
It took a little longer than expected, but who cares?
I'm sure it's nice... but now that I'm driving, I'm wondering if I haven't been driving long enough...
Mostly requests.
Thank you. Ai, you just drove straight through, right?
Yes, it was an easy road.
The Kaki-ya we visited this time is located in Itoshima, Fukuoka Prefecture.
Zauo Barbecue Garden Itoshima
Here you can enjoy oysters, a variety of seafood, and hearty meats right in front of the sea!
and hearty meats right in front of the sea!
There are many popular photo spots on the beach.
There are many popular photo spots on the sandy beach, so the place is crowded with customers every day!
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
Sparkling
Sparkling!
I want some.
This one.
It's the same color as Riko's.
This?
It's rare.
I'll have a turban shell.
Want some?
Sorry.
Thank you.
You're really going to say that?
Kachiko!
I already asked for it.
Let's burn it.
You're fast.
I guess you don't have a palate for this.
I'll grill it.
I'm going to grill oysters because they're oysters.
I'll grill pumpkins too.
Pumpkin? What? There it is.
But let's cook the oysters first.
I'm sure we'll burn the pumpkins.
That's right.
Okay, let's do it.
Flat side down.
First things first.
Wow.
You too, Ai.
Okay, thank you.
Ready?
You ready?
I'm going for it.
Here you go.
Here we go.
So, about a minute.
One minute.
Did I put this in last?
Whatever.
It's in the middle.
There it is.
That was quick.
I'll flip it over when it's open.
Oh, no, it's too late now.
Oh, my God.
It's an explosion!
I guess we're good to go.
This area sure looks nice.
Okay, I'll just take the first one that's open.
Looks scary...
It's ready!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
It's amazing!
Is it hot?
Looks hot.
Poof!
Looks so good, it's so soft and juicy.
Oh, it's so good!
Looks so soft and juicy.
Looks so good!
Well, I'll just go with it.
Aimon, let's go as we are.
First things first.
Wow, you're pretty solid.
Wow!
Oh, wow!
Purr-fect!
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
It's so delicious!
The taste is so rich!
It's so soft and crunchy! It's so soft and crunchy!
It's so rich in flavor, and it's so soft and crunchy!
Delicious!
It's almost gone.
It was only for a moment.
I'll have another.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy!
It looks warm.
How's your partner? Oh, my God!
Is it good?
Hey! Thank you! You're so real.
It's so sparkly.
Meraldo, you smell like soy sauce! I do, don't I?
Here, hard turban shell.
Not hard, not hard.
Not hard. - Oh, why is that an eye? It's not an eye.
I found some amazing colors.
We can't eat this, right?
Yes, you can.
Oh!
I can hear it.
That's kind of scary.
You're still alive.
Huh.
Did we get this?
It's really deep in there.
It's not bitter, it's not bitter. It's that good, it's so good, it's so good.
It's not bitter, it's not bitter.
It's not bitter, it's not bitter. It's that way.
It's all gone.
I got it.
It's not bitter.
What's good?
Bitter!
bitter
Bitter
Bitter, bitter, bitter, bitter, can you go? Not bitter?
Something sweet and bitter?
It's good.
How was your day?
It was fun.
It was like I wasn't driving today... all the way to the Amazon station... but it was really delicious.
It's been a while since I've had the pleasure of riding with you guys... but I thought I'd be nervous... but we talked like we always do.
I'm glad we were able to talk like we usually do.
I thought I'd be nervous but we talked like we always do and it was great!
I've been to Izumo-taisha a lot.
Is it far?
You went a lot.
Not at all.
Drive.
If you say so, Ai.
It's fine.
Okay.
I'm sorry.